{
    "subject": "Param_Gill",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Hotel_Hollywood",
    "human_readable": "Param Gill directed Hotel Hollywood.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8961890935897827,
            "question": "Has Param Gill won any awards for directing Hotel Hollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7778193950653076,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Hotel Hollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.752631425857544,
            "question": "Is Param Gill a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.715114176273346,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Param Gill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6696839332580566,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Param Gill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47759976983070374,
            "question": "Who are the actors in Hotel Hollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4448378384113312,
            "question": "What is the plot of Hotel Hollywood about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4381546676158905,
            "question": "Where was Hotel Hollywood filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3493312895298004,
            "question": "When was Hotel Hollywood released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26201751828193665,
            "question": "What genre is Hotel Hollywood likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Param Gill directed Hotel Hollywood.",
            "html": "yago_19134_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Hotel Hollywood released?",
            "html": "yago_19134_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Hotel Hollywood filmed?",
            "html": "yago_19134_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of Hotel Hollywood about?",
            "html": "yago_19134_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19134_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There are multiple mentions of a film called \"Hotel Hollywood\" and its director, but it's not clear from the documents who the director is. However, one mention in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_19134/re-ranker-msmarco/80.txt says that the film was directed by Param Gill.\n* Another mention in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_19134/re-ranker-msmarco/107.txt also confirms that Param Gill made a movie called \"Hotel Hollywood\".\n\nBased on this information, I conclude that:\n\n{ \"output\": \"yes\" }"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"Param Gill Directed the movie 'Hotel Hollywood'\", which directly supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}